autoweb.co.uk 2011-03-13

# Untitled Document

**AUTOWEB.CO.UK**

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms and Conditions of use provided on our Legal Notice. Capitalised words in this Privacy Policy are defined in our Legal Notice. 

Autoweb is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. 

The information we collect from you is only that required by us and/or our Partners in order to provide you with the information you have requested. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we do not supply your Personal Information to any other person unless you have expressly authorised us to do so. 

By registering to use the Services and by using the Site generally you will be deemed to consent to our use of your Personal Information in the ways as detailed in this Privacy Policy. 

**Personal Information**

Autoweb.co.uk is a partnership registered with the Information Commissioner to collect data under the Data Protection Act 1998. All Personal Information you supply will be treated in accordance with that Act. We will not pass on your Personal Information to any other person except when we believe the law requires or with your consent as set out in this Privacy Policy. To this end, we may pass your information to our Partners and agents authorised to act for us and on our behalf and to other third parties. When registering with us, you must provide your e-mail address, title, name, telephone number and to create a password. The information collected on the Registration Form may be used to send messages (including via e-mail and sms messaging) for the following purposes: 

  * to allow us to send messages to you when managing enquiries on line; 
  * to allow is to contact you for user service, if necessary; 
  * to customise the content of the Site to meet your specific needs; 
  * to make product improvements to the our Service; 
  * to keep you informed of new features and products and services available form third parties where you have specifically opted to receive this information. 

If you do not wish to receive notice of site upgrades, enhancements, new features, user tips, additional information on products and services from us and/or our Partners you may opt-out of this facility during the registration process. If you choose not to receive such information at any later date, please contact us at [contact@autoweb.co.uk](mailto:contact@autoweb.co.uk)

**General information**

In general we gather data about all of our users collectively, such as what areas and services users visit most frequently. We only use such data in the aggregate. We may record and share non-personal aggregated data with our Partners in order to determine what is most beneficial for our users and how we can continually improve the Autoweb user experience. 

[ **Co-branded Pages**

Any information that you enter onto a co-branded page may become the property of both us and the co-branded Partner. In that instance, Autoweb is not responsible for any of the information received by our Partner. In some instances Personal Information may be passed from us to our Partners on order to automatically pre-fill fields on their websites. While we make all efforts to protect your privacy when negotiating our partnerships, we are not responsible for their use of your Personal Information. To that end, we encourage you to read our Partners’ privacy statements or request them directly from our Partners in the event they are not readily available.] 

**User Responses**

**Online surveys**

Autoweb.co.uk value the opinions and comments of our users, so from time to time we may conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional for all users. Typically the information is aggregated and used to make improvements to the Site and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for all users. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey. 

**Feedback**

Please submit any feedback to us. Feedback is used primarily for internal purposes to aid us in improving the Site. Any feedback submitted becomes the property of Autoweb.co.uk. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the Site. We will seek your written or e-mail approval should we want to use your personal success story for marketing purposes. 

**Information Collection**

**Cookies**

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies in several ways; to allow you to log in, to keep track of your preferences and for us to track usage of the Site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. 

**IP addresses**

We may collect IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration. We shall only use these addresses for technical and tracking purposes unless otherwise required by the law. 

**Log files**

We capture industry standard information solely for the purposes of analysis. Information contained in log files is intended for internal use only and will not be disclosed to our Partners. The aggregate logged information is not linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**Hosting**

This Site is hosted for us by Donhost Ltd, 1 Heather Court, Doncaster, DN2 5YL. 

**Enquiries**

If you have any enquiries about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [contact@autoweb.co.uk](mailto:contact@autoweb.co.uk), or in writing to: 

Autoweb 

4 The Crescent

Selby 

North Yorkshire 

YO8 4PU

Customer Services at 01757 701010 (Monday to Friday between 9.00am and 5.30pm) 

Thank you for using Autoweb.co.uk
